

ROMAN STAKHIV

Full-Stack & QAQ Engineer

- ✓ roma.stakhiv@gmail.com
- **>** +380 (96) 000 23 63
- Kyiv, Ukraine
- roma-stakhiv.vercel.app
- in linkedin.com/in/romchik-stakhiv
- github.com/RomchikSt

SKILLS

HTML & CSS

JavaScript & TypeScript

React & Next.js

Shopify & Wordpress

React Native

Node.js & Express

Supabase

MongoDB

Git & GitHub

Cypress & Playwright

Cucumber

Postman

Jenkins & Docker

LANGUAGES

Ukrainian

English

HOBBIES

- Tennis
- Chess

PROFILE

I am a Full Stack and AQA Engineer. My experience covers the creation of attractive websites, web applications, cross-platform mobile applications, and their automated testing. Some of my various projects are in the Portfolio.

I specialize in developing cross-browser and cross-platform applications, ensuring they work optimally in different environments. I also do automated testing, which allows me to ensure a high level of product quality and reliability. This integrated approach allows you to achieve high performance and reliability in both application development and testing.

I am constantly learning new technologies, which allows me to effectively solve the challenges of modern projects, ensuring flexibility and a high level of quality in development and testing.

In my free time, I play tennis and chess, which helps me develop strategic thinking and concentration. In addition, I love active recreation in the fresh air, which gives me energy and inspires new projects.

EDUCATION

Magister, Mechanical Engineering

National University of Food Technologies, Kyiv

2010 - 2015

EMPLOYMENT

Liberty Dev

Jun 2023 - Present

Full-Stack & AQA Engineer, Kyiv

I am engaged in the development of highly functional web and mobile applications and their optimization. Effectively integrated advanced front-end and back-end solutions using JavaScript, React, Node.js and other modern technologies. I also build websites using WordPress and Shopify. Creation of test automation using Cypress, Playwright and Postman, which ensures high quality and performance of applications. I develop detailed plans and scenarios of automated tests for

regression and integration testing, which contributes to the stable and efficient operation of the system.

Skills: TypeScript, React ,Redux, Framer Motion, i18next, Material UI, Node.js, MySQL, Cypress, Postman, Wordpress, Shopify

Noname Digital

Apr 2024 - Present

QA Engineer, Kyiv

Manual testing of mobile applications. Experienced in identifying, documenting, and reporting bugs to ensure optimal application quality and user experience. Executes detailed test plans and cases covering functional, regression, and acceptance testing. Works closely with development teams using various testing methodologies to ensure high application quality